John (Sales Rep): Hi Sarah, thanks for taking the time to meet with me today. How are you doing?
Sarah (Prospect): Hi John, I'm doing well, thanks. I'm looking forward to learning more about your solution.
John: Great! Before we dive in, can you tell me a bit about your current reporting process and any challenges you're facing?
Sarah: Sure. We're spending about 15 hours a week on manual reporting, and errors are creeping in. It's becoming a real bottleneck for our team.
John: That sounds frustrating. 15 hours a week is significant. What kind of impact are these errors having on your business?
Sarah: Well, we've had to redo reports twice this month, and it's affecting our decision-making speed. Management is getting concerned.
John: I understand. Let me show you how our solution can help. I'll walk you through our ROI calculator step by step.
Sarah: That sounds helpful. I love how you walked through the ROI calculator step by step. That really helped me understand the value.
John: I'm glad that was useful. Now, what's your timeline for making a decision on this type of solution?
Sarah: Well, we're looking at a few different solutions right now. We need to make a decision by the end of the quarter.
John: That's great to hear. What factors are most important to you when evaluating these different options?
Sarah: Cost is definitely a factor, but we're more focused on reliability and ease of implementation. Our IT team is pretty stretched thin right now with the ERP rollout.
John: I completely understand about IT bandwidth. What kind of support would you need during implementation to make this successful?
Sarah: We'd need hands-on support and training. I'd also need to see how this integrates with our existing CRM system.
John: Absolutely. We have a dedicated implementation team that works closely with clients. For CRM integration, we have pre-built connectors for most major systems.
Sarah: That's reassuring. Budget is always a consideration, but if the ROI is there and implementation is smooth, I think we could make this work.
John: I appreciate your transparency. Based on what you've shared, I think our solution could save you significant time and reduce those error rates.
Sarah: It definitely sounds promising. What would be the next steps if we wanted to move forward?
John: I'd like to schedule a technical demo with your IT team to show the CRM integration capabilities. Would that be helpful?
Sarah: Yes, that would be perfect. I'd need to see how this integrates with our existing CRM. Can we set something up for next week?